[
    { "question" : "Olmak", "answer" : "To be", "pronunciation" : "/oɫmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Gitmek", "answer" : "To go", "pronunciation" : "/ɡitmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Gelmek", "answer" : "To come", "pronunciation" : "/ɟelmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "İstemek", "answer" : "To want", "pronunciation" : "/isteme̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Yapmak", "answer" : "To do", "pronunciation" : "/jɑpmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Almak", "answer" : "To take", "pronunciation" : "/ɑɫmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Vermek", "answer" : "To give", "pronunciation" : "/vɛɾmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Görmek", "answer" : "To see", "pronunciation" : "/ɟøɾmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Bulunmak", "answer" : "To be found", "pronunciation" : "/bulunmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Konuşmak", "answer" : "To speak", "pronunciation" : "/konuʃmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Etmek", "answer" : "To do", "pronunciation" : "/etmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Anlamak", "answer" : "To understand", "pronunciation" : "/ɑnɫɑmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Sevmek", "answer" : "To love", "pronunciation" : "/se̞vmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Beklemek", "answer" : "To wait", "pronunciation" : "/beklemek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "İçmek", "answer" : "To drink", "pronunciation" : "/itʃmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Yemek", "answer" : "To eat", "pronunciation" : "/jeme̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Düşünmek", "answer" : "To think", "pronunciation" : "/dʊʃynmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Bulmak", "answer" : "To find", "pronunciation" : "/buɫmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "İstememek", "answer" : "To not want", "pronunciation" : "/istememe̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Geçmek", "answer" : "To pass", "pronunciation" : "/ɟetʃmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Açmak", "answer" : "To open", "pronunciation" : "/ɑtʃmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Kapatmak", "answer" : "To close", "pronunciation" : "/kɑpɑtmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Kullanmak", "answer" : "To use", "pronunciation" : "/kullanmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Yazmak", "answer" : "To write", "pronunciation" : "/jɑzmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Okumak", "answer" : "To read", "pronunciation" : "/oku̞mɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Öğrenmek", "answer" : "To learn", "pronunciation" : "/ø̞ʁenmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Anlatmak", "answer" : "To tell", "pronunciation" : "/ɑnɫɑtmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "İşlemek", "answer" : "To process", "pronunciation" : "/iʃlemek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Çalışmak", "answer" : "To work", "pronunciation" : "/tʃɑɫiʃmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Satmak", "answer" : "To sell", "pronunciation" : "/sɑtmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Alışveriş yapmak", "answer" : "To go shopping", "pronunciation" : "/ɑɫɯʃveɾiʃ jɑpmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Uyumak", "answer" : "To sleep", "pronunciation" : "/ujumɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Dinlemek", "answer" : "To listen", "pronunciation" : "/dɪnlemek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Kalkmak", "answer" : "To get up", "pronunciation" : "/kɑɫkmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Yıkamak", "answer" : "To wash", "pronunciation" : "/jikɑmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Gezmek", "answer" : "To walk around", "pronunciation" : "/ɟezmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Ödemek", "answer" : "To pay", "pronunciation" : "/ø̞demek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Seçmek", "answer" : "To choose", "pronunciation" : "/se̞tʃmek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Bakmak", "answer" : "To look", "pronunciation" : "/bɑkmɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "İzlemek", "answer" : "To watch", "pronunciation" : "/i̞zlemek/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "Ev", "answer" : "House", "pronunciation" : "/ev/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kişi", "answer" : "Person", "pronunciation" : "/kiʃi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Hayat", "answer" : "Life", "pronunciation" : "/hɑjɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "İş", "answer" : "Job", "pronunciation" : "/iʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Su", "answer" : "Water", "pronunciation" : "/su/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Yemek", "answer" : "Food", "pronunciation" : "/jeme̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Para", "answer" : "Money", "pronunciation" : "/pɑɾɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Saat", "answer" : "Hour", "pronunciation" : "/sɑːt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Anne", "answer" : "Mother", "pronunciation" : "/ɑnne̞/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Baba", "answer" : "Father", "pronunciation" : "/bɑbɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Çocuk", "answer" : "Child", "pronunciation" : "/tʃødʒuk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Okul", "answer" : "School", "pronunciation" : "/oku̞l/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kitap", "answer" : "Book", "pronunciation" : "/kitɑp/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Film", "answer" : "Movie", "pronunciation" : "/film/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Yol", "answer" : "Road", "pronunciation" : "/jol/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Araba", "answer" : "Car", "pronunciation" : "/ɑɾɑbɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Şehir", "answer" : "City", "pronunciation" : "/ʃehiɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Ülke", "answer" : "Country", "pronunciation" : "/y̞lke̞/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kedi", "answer" : "Cat", "pronunciation" : "/ke̞di/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Köpek", "answer" : "Dog", "pronunciation" : "/kø̞pɛk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Top", "answer" : "Ball", "pronunciation" : "/top/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Renk", "answer" : "Color", "pronunciation" : "/ɾen̪k/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Sevgili", "answer" : "Beloved", "pronunciation" : "/se̞vɟili/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Aile", "answer" : "Family", "pronunciation" : "/ɑile̞/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Sağlık", "answer" : "Health", "pronunciation" : "/sɑːɫik/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Eğlence", "answer" : "Entertainment", "pronunciation" : "/e̞ɫɟence̞/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Market", "answer" : "Market", "pronunciation" : "/mɑɾket/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Şarkı", "answer" : "Song", "pronunciation" : "/ʃɑɾcɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Dans", "answer" : "Dance", "pronunciation" : "/dɑns/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Bahar", "answer" : "Spring", "pronunciation" : "/bɑhɑɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Yaz", "answer" : "Summer", "pronunciation" : "/jɑz/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kış", "answer" : "Winter", "pronunciation" : "/kɯʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Güz", "answer" : "Autumn", "pronunciation" : "/ɟy̞z/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Tatil", "answer" : "Vacation", "pronunciation" : "/tɑtiɫ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Dünya", "answer" : "World", "pronunciation" : "/dʊɲjɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Gözlük", "answer" : "Glasses", "pronunciation" : "/ɡø̞zly̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Çanta", "answer" : "Bag", "pronunciation" : "/tʃɑntɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Kıyafet", "answer" : "Clothes", "pronunciation" : "/kɯjɑfet/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Ayakkabı", "answer" : "Shoes", "pronunciation" : "/ɑjɑkkɑbɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Telefon", "answer" : "Telephone", "pronunciation" : "/tele̞fɔn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Televizyon", "answer" : "Television", "pronunciation" : "/te̞levizjo̞n/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Bilgisayar", "answer" : "Computer", "pronunciation" : "/bi̞lɡisɑ̈ːɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Müzik", "answer" : "Music", "pronunciation" : "/my̞zik/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Otobüs", "answer" : "Bus", "pronunciation" : "/oto̞by̞s/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Metro", "answer" : "Subway", "pronunciation" : "/metro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Uçak", "answer" : "Airplane", "pronunciation" : "/utʃɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "Güzel", "answer" : "Beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/ɟyzel/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "İyi", "answer" : "Good", "pronunciation" : "/ijɪ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kötü", "answer" : "Bad", "pronunciation" : "/kø̞ty̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Büyük", "answer" : "Big", "pronunciation" : "/by̞jyk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Küçük", "answer" : "Small", "pronunciation" : "/kycyk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Yeni", "answer" : "New", "pronunciation" : "/jeni/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Eski", "answer" : "Old", "pronunciation" : "/e̞ski/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Sıcak", "answer" : "Hot", "pronunciation" : "/sɯdʒɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Soğuk", "answer" : "Cold", "pronunciation" : "/so̞ːɫyk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kirli", "answer" : "Dirty", "pronunciation" : "/ki̞ɾli̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Temiz", "answer" : "Clean", "pronunciation" : "/te̞miz/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kolay", "answer" : "Easy", "pronunciation" : "/ko̞ɫɑj/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Zor", "answer" : "Difficult", "pronunciation" : "/zo̞ɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Hızlı", "answer" : "Fast", "pronunciation" : "/hɯzɫɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Yavaş", "answer" : "Slow", "pronunciation" : "/jɑvɑʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Gürültülü", "answer" : "Noisy", "pronunciation" : "/ɟyɾylty̞lü/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Sessiz", "answer" : "Quiet", "pronunciation" : "/se̞ssiz/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Pahalı", "answer" : "Expensive", "pronunciation" : "/pɑhɑɫɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ucuz", "answer" : "Cheap", "pronunciation" : "/utʃuz/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Lezzetli", "answer" : "Tasty", "pronunciation" : "/lezetli/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Acı", "answer" : "Spicy", "pronunciation" : "/ɑdʒɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Tatlı", "answer" : "Sweet", "pronunciation" : "/tɑtɫɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Tuzlu", "answer" : "Salty", "pronunciation" : "/tuzlu/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Kuru", "answer" : "Dry", "pronunciation" : "/kuɾu/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Islak", "answer" : "Wet", "pronunciation" : "/is̪l̪ɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Canlı", "answer" : "Alive", "pronunciation" : "/dʒɑnɫɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ölü", "answer" : "Dead", "pronunciation" : "/ø̞ly̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Ağır", "answer" : "Heavy", "pronunciation" : "/ɑːɾɯɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Hafif", "answer" : "Light", "pronunciation" : "/hɑfi̞f/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Geniş", "answer" : "Wide", "pronunciation" : "/ɟeni̞ʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Dar", "answer" : "Narrow", "pronunciation" : "/dɑɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Derin", "answer" : "Deep", "pronunciation" : "/de̞ɾin/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Yüzeysel", "answer" : "Superficial", "pronunciation" : "/jy̞ze̞ysel/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Yakın", "answer" : "Close", "pronunciation" : "/jɑki̞n/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Uzak", "answer" : "Far", "pronunciation" : "/uzɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Koloni", "answer" : "Crowded", "pronunciation" : "/koloni/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Boş", "answer" : "Empty", "pronunciation" : "/boʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Dolu", "answer" : "Full", "pronunciation" : "/do̞ɫu/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Sağlam", "answer" : "Solid", "pronunciation" : "/sɑːɫɑm/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Zayıf", "answer" : "Weak", "pronunciation" : "/zɑjɯf/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Büyülü", "answer" : "Magical", "pronunciation" : "/by̞jylü/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Rengarenk", "answer" : "Colorful", "pronunciation" : "/ɾe̞ŋɡɑɾe̞n̪k/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "Şimdi", "answer" : "Now", "pronunciation" : "/ʃimd̪i/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Hemen", "answer" : "Immediately", "pronunciation" : "/he̞me̞n/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Daha", "answer" : "More", "pronunciation" : "/d̪ɑhɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Az", "answer" : "Few", "pronunciation" : "/ɑz/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Çok", "answer" : "Very", "pronunciation" : "/tʃo̞k/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Sık sık", "answer" : "Often", "pronunciation" : "/sik sik/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nadiren", "answer" : "Rarely", "pronunciation" : "/nɑdi̞ɾen/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Şöyle", "answer" : "Like this", "pronunciation" : "/ʃøjle̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Böyle", "answer" : "Like this", "pronunciation" : "/bøjle̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Orada", "answer" : "There", "pronunciation" : "/o̞ɾɑd̪ɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Burada", "answer" : "Here", "pronunciation" : "/buɾad̪ɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nereye", "answer" : "Where to", "pronunciation" : "/neɾe̞je/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nerede", "answer" : "Where", "pronunciation" : "/neɾede̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Ne zaman", "answer" : "When", "pronunciation" : "/ne̞ zaman/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Her zaman", "answer" : "Always", "pronunciation" : "/he̞ɾ zaman/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Hiçbir zaman", "answer" : "Never", "pronunciation" : "/hitʃbiɾ zaman/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Geçen hafta", "answer" : "Last week", "pronunciation" : "/ge̞tʃen hɑftɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Bu hafta", "answer" : "This week", "pronunciation" : "/bu hɑftɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Geçen yıl", "answer" : "Last year", "pronunciation" : "/ge̞tʃen jɯɫ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Bu yıl", "answer" : "This year", "pronunciation" : "/bu jɯɫ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Dün", "answer" : "Yesterday", "pronunciation" : "/d̪yn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Bugün", "answer" : "Today", "pronunciation" : "/buɡyn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Yarın", "answer" : "Tomorrow", "pronunciation" : "/jɑɾɯn/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Neden", "answer" : "Why", "pronunciation" : "/ne̞den/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Nasıl", "answer" : "How", "pronunciation" : "/nɑsɯɫ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Kesinlikle", "answer" : "Definitely", "pronunciation" : "/kesinlikle/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Belki", "answer" : "Maybe", "pronunciation" : "/be̞lki/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Yavaşça", "answer" : "Slowly", "pronunciation" : "/jɑvɑʃtʃɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Hızlıca", "answer" : "Quickly", "pronunciation" : "/hɯzɫy̞tʃɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Açıkça", "answer" : "Clearly", "pronunciation" : "/ɑtʃykʤɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Kapalı", "answer" : "Closed", "pronunciation" : "/kɑpɑɫɯ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Açık", "answer" : "Open", "pronunciation" : "/ɑtʃyk/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Yaklaşık", "answer" : "Approximately", "pronunciation" : "/jɑklɑʃɯk/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Tamamen", "answer" : "Completely", "pronunciation" : "/tɑmɑmen/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Fazla", "answer" : "Too much", "pronunciation" : "/fɑzlɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Yeterince", "answer" : "Enough", "pronunciation" : "/jɛte̞ɾince̞/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Asla", "answer" : "Never", "pronunciation" : "/ɑsɫɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "İlk olarak", "answer" : "Firstly", "pronunciation" : "/i̞lk o̞laɾɯt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Son olarak", "answer" : "Lastly", "pronunciation" : "/so̞n o̞laɾɯt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "Ve", "answer" : "And", "pronunciation" : "/ve/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ama", "answer" : "But", "pronunciation" : "/ɑmɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ya da", "answer" : "Or", "pronunciation" : "/jɑ dɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Fakat", "answer" : "However", "pronunciation" : "/fɑkɑt/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Hem", "answer" : "Both", "pronunciation" : "/hem/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Veya", "answer" : "Either", "pronunciation" : "/vejɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ancak", "answer" : "Only", "pronunciation" : "/ɑntʃɑk/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Oysa", "answer" : "Whereas", "pronunciation" : "/ojʃɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Nitekim", "answer" : "Indeed", "pronunciation" : "/nitekim/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Zira", "answer" : "For", "pronunciation" : "/ziɾɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Dolayısıyla", "answer" : "Therefore", "pronunciation" : "/d̪olɑjisjɑlɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Yani", "answer" : "That is", "pronunciation" : "/jɑni/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "De", "answer" : "Also", "pronunciation" : "/de/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Göre", "answer" : "According to", "pronunciation" : "/ɟøɾe/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Eğer", "answer" : "If", "pronunciation" : "/e̞ɟæɾ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "İse", "answer" : "Then", "pronunciation" : "/i̞se̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ki", "answer" : "That", "pronunciation" : "/ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Madem ki", "answer" : "Since", "pronunciation" : "/mɑdem ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Nedeniyle", "answer" : "Because of", "pronunciation" : "/ne̞deni̞le̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ayrıca", "answer" : "Additionally", "pronunciation" : "/ɑjɾɯdʒɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Buna göre", "answer" : "Accordingly", "pronunciation" : "/bunɑ ɟøɾe/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Eğer ki", "answer" : "In case", "pronunciation" : "/e̞ɟæɾ ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Halbuki", "answer" : "Whereas", "pronunciation" : "/hɑɫbuki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Hatta", "answer" : "Even", "pronunciation" : "/hɑtɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Mesela", "answer" : "For example", "pronunciation" : "/meselɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Ne var ki", "answer" : "However", "pronunciation" : "/ne̞ vɑɾ ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "O halde", "answer" : "So", "pronunciation" : "/o̞ hɑlde̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Tam aksine", "answer" : "On the contrary", "pronunciation" : "/tɑm ɑksine̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Üstelik", "answer" : "Moreover", "pronunciation" : "/yste̞lik/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Yalnız", "answer" : "Only", "pronunciation" : "/jɑlnɯz/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Yine de", "answer" : "Still", "pronunciation" : "/jine̞ de̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Diğer yandan", "answer" : "On the other hand", "pronunciation" : "/di̞ɟe̞ɾ jɑndɑn/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Sonuçta", "answer" : "In conclusion", "pronunciation" : "/sonu̞tʃtɑ/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Çünkü", "answer" : "Because", "pronunciation" : "/tʃynky̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Kaldı ki", "answer" : "Moreover", "pronunciation" : "/kɑɫdɯ ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Nihayetinde", "answer" : "Eventually", "pronunciation" : "/ni̞hɑjetinde̞/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "O zaman", "answer" : "Then", "pronunciation" : "/o̞ zɑmɑn/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Yani ki", "answer" : "That is to say", "pronunciation" : "/jɑni ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "Öyle ki", "answer" : "So that", "pronunciation" : "/øjle̞ ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]